Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Campaign Records, 1969; Series VII
    - Press Releases - Subject
      - Graves endorsement, joint statement, election day (George Ball, R. Gilpatrick, Cyrus Vance (Box 135, Folder 94)
      - Haitian - Americans endorsement (Box 135, Folder 95)
      - Halloween party (Box 135, Folder 96)
      - Health (Box 135, Folder 97)
      - "Health-In" (Box 135, Folder 98)
      - Hispanic Societies endorsement (Box 135, Folder 99)
      - Human Resourses Administration (Box 136, Folder 100-101)
      - Hospitals (Box 136, Folder 102)
      - Housing (Box 136, Folder 103)
      - Hutton, Mrs. Edward (Box 136, Folder 104)
      - Jones, J. Raymond (Box 136, Folder 105)
      - Katzman (Box 136, Folder 106)
      - Kearing, Samuel Jr., endorsement (Box 136, Folder 107)
      - Labor (Box 136, Folder 108)
      - Labor relations (Box 136, Folder 109)
      - Labor unions endorsements (Box 136, Folder 110)
      - Lawyers Committee (Box 136, Folder 111)
      - Legislation, state, national, local (Box 136, Folder 112)
      - Lehman, Mrs. Herbert, endorsement (Box 136, Folder 113)
      - Lindsay accepts TV debates (Box 136, Folder 114)
      - Lindsay assails Procaccino, ducks debates (Box 136, Folder 115)
      - Lindsay biography (Box 136, Folder 116)
      - Lindsay campaign kick-off raly speech, Queens, Sep 1 (Box 136, Folder 117)
      - Lindsay crime statement, Mario Procaccino (Box 136, Folder 118)
      - Lindsay decision to run (Box 136, Folder 119)
      - Lindsay Gala (Box 136, Folder 120)
      - Lindsay, Kiwanis leaders, speech to (Box 136, Folder 121)
      - Lindsay record, called best of any first term mayor (Box 136, Folder 122)
      - Lindsay, Madison Square Garden speech (Box 136, Folder 123)
      - Mayor's Office (Box 136, Folder 124-126)
      - Mayor's press conference (Box 137, Folder 127)
      - Mayor's press releases (Box 137, Folder 128)
      - Mayor's press releases (Box 137, Folder 129)
      - MacArthur, General Douglas, Republican Club endorsement (Box 137, Folder 130)
      - Manhattan Republican Club endorsement (Box 137, Folder 131)
      - Martin Luther King endorsement (Box 137, Folder 132)
      - Maxwell's Plum pre-election buffet (Box 137, Folder 133)
      - Men's Club - Shaare Torah (Brooklyn) speech (Box 137, Folder 134)
      - Minority groups (Box 137, Folder 135)
      - Miscellaneous, memoranda on press office activities (Box 137, Folder 136)
      - Miscellaneous, not campaign office (Box 137, Folder 137)
      - Moon Watch clean-up (Box 137, Folder 138)
      - "Moratorium" proclamation (Box 137, Folder 139)
      - Political (Box 137, Folder 140)
      - Post primary statement (Box 137, Folder 141)
      - Speeches (Box 137, Folder 142)
      - University, Long Island, Young Democrats endorsement (Box 137, Folder 143)
      - New Democratic Coalition (Box 137, Folder 144)
      - News releases, Gracie Mansion, Police (Box 137, Folder 145)
      - "New York Women's Place is not in the Home" (Box 138, Folder 146)
      - Organizational Democratic Leaders endorsement (Box 138, Folder 147)
      - Parks, recreation and culture (Box 138, Folder 148)
      - Patrolman's fund, missing money, rainstorm, Queens nurses, Mrs. Lou Gehrig, Assemblyman Passannante, Garcia, Goldin (Box 138, Folder 149)
      - Perrotta assails Marchi (Box 138, Folder 150)
      - Perrotta on Battista (Box 138, Folder 151)
      - Perrotta charges Battista (Box 138, Folder 152-153)
      - Perrotta charges Marchi conservatism (Box 138, Folder 154)
      - Perrotta, Citizen's Union (Box 138, Folder 155)
      - Perrotta, finance statement (Box 138, Folder 156)
      - Perrotaa - Garelik (Box 138, Folder 157)
      - Perrotta, press reform program (Box 138, Folder 158)
      - Perrotaa, St. Anthony Festival (Box 138, Folder 159)
      - Perrotta, telegram to Secretary of Treasury Kennedy (Box 138, Folder 160)
      - Petitions (Box 138, Folder 161)
      - Pharmacists endorsement (Box 138, Folder 162)
      - Philippine Organization endorsement (Box 138, Folder 163)
      - Posters for Lindsay (Box 138, Folder 164)
      - Police (Box 138, Folder 165)
      - Police, law enforcement, crime (Box 138, Folder 166)
      - Police (4th platoon) (Box 138, Folder 167)
      - Political files #8, campaign headquarters (Box 138, Folder 168)
      - Press conference (Box 138, Folder 169)
      - Press release, 38th street opening (Box 138, Folder 170)
      - Press release, volunteers (Box 138, Folder 171)
      - Proccacino, Mario, transcript of television news release (Box 138, Folder 172)
      - Public, private cooperation (Box 138, Folder 173)
      - Puerto Rican civic and community leader's endorsement (Box 138, Folder 174)
      - Queens accomplishments (Box 138, Folder 175)
      - Queens, clean-up at Fort Filder (Box 138, Folder 176)
      - Queens Coalition endorsement (Box 138, Folder 177)
      - Queens College speech, Vietnam (Box 138, Folder 178)
      - Queens County Republican dinner (Box 138, Folder 179)
      - Queens, C. Greitzer, F. Leichter, T. Weiss endorsement, JVL gains support (Box 138, Folder 180)
      - Queens support, Kennedy - King Club, Eleanor Roosevelt Reform Club, north Shore Club (Box 138, Folder 181)
      - Queens newspaper article (Box 138, Folder 182)
      - Queens, 22nd A.D. Republican Club endorsement (Box 139, Folder 183)
      - Republicans for Lindsay (Box 139, Folder 184)
      - Riverdale, Benjamin Franklin Reform Democratic Club endorsement (Box 139, Folder 185)
      - Riverdale rally (Box 139, Folder 186)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, Reform Democratic Club endorsement (Box 139, Folder 187)
      - Roosevelt Kingsborough Independent Democratic Club endorsement (Box 139, Folder 188)
      - SANE endorsement (Box 139, Folder 189)
      - Seymour Posner endorsement (Bronx Democrate) (Box 139, Folder 190)
      - Six labor union endorsement (Box 139, Folder 191)
      - Social workers endorsement (Box 139, Folder 192)
      - Student campaigning in Catskills (Box 139, Folder 193)
      - Student begin canvassing campaign (Box 139, Folder 194)
      - Supplementary filing of petitions (Box 139, Folder 195)
      - Sutton, Percy E., endorsement (Manhattan borough president) (Box 139, Folder 196)
      - Swoboda, Ron, volunteers (Box 139, Folder 197)
      - Terminal Employees Civil Service union endorsement (Box 139, Folder 198)
      - Transit Fraternal Association endorsement (Box 139, Folder 199)
      - Transportation (Box 139, Folder 200)
      - TV special on New York (Box 139, Folder 201)
      - Variety evening, St. Michael's Home, Staten Island (Box 139, Folder 202)
      - Variety show, volunteers, Staten Island, MT. Loretto Home (Box 139, Folder 203)
      - Variety show, Clearview Nursing Home, Queens (Box 139, Folder 204)
      - Vietnam (Box 139, Folder 205)
      - Volunteer activities, artists, athletes, Giants, Health-In, etc. (Box 139, Folder 206)
      - Volunteer activities for week of Sep 2 to Sep 5 (Box 139, Folder 207)
      - Volunteers press conference (Box 139, Folder 208)
      - Volunteers, variety show (Box 139, Folder 209)
      - "Who's That With John Lindsay?" (Box 139, Folder 210)
      - Young and Republican (Box 139, Folder 211)
      - Young Republicans, Bronx endorsement (Box 139, Folder 212)
      - Young Republican Club, Eastside, endorsement (Box 139, Folder 213)
      - Young Republicans, Richmond, endorsement (Box 139, Folder 214)
      - Zabel, Eleanor - biography (Box 139, Folder 215)
    - Press Releases - Chronological
      - Chronological index, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 216)
      - Subject index, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 217)
      - Chronological index, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 218)
      - Subject index, 1967 (Box 140, Folder 219)
      - Chronological index, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 220)
      - Subject index, 1968 (Box 140, Folder 221)
      - Subject index, 1968 January-July (Box 140, Folder 222-228)
      - Subject index, 1968 August-December (Box 141, Folder 229-233)
      - Chronological index, 1969 (Box 141, Folder 234)
      - Subject index, 1969 (Box 141, Folder 235)
      - Subject index, 1969 January-April (Box 141, Folder 236-241)
      - Subject index
        - 1969 May-September 1969 May-September (Box 142, Folder 242-251)
        - 1969 October 1969 October (Box 143, Folder 252-256)
    - News Clippings
      - 1969 March-April (Box 144, Folder 257-270)
      - 1969 April 20 - May (Box 145, Folder 271-286)
      - 1969 May 12 - June 2 (Box 146, Folder 287-309)
      - 1969 June 2-23 (Box 147, Folder 310-326)
      - 1969 June - August 1 (Box 148, Folder 327-347)
      - 1969 August - September 1-8 (Box 149, Folder 348-368)
      - 1969 September - October 6 (Box 150, Folder 369-375)
      - 1969 October 7-29 (Box 151, Folder 376-385)
      - 1969 October - November 1 (Box 152, Folder 386-389)
      - Advertisements, Beame (Box 153, Folder 390)
      - Advertisements, Garelik, Lindsay (Box 153, Folder 391)
      - Advertisements, Lindsay, anti-ads (Box 153, Folder 392)
      - Advertisements, Marchi (Box 153, Folder 393)
      - Advertisements, Procaccino (Box 153, Folder 394)
      - Advertisements, Smith (Box 153, Folder 395)
      - Magazine articles (Box 153, Folder 396)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 153, Folder 397-402)
      - Urban Coalition (Box 153, Folder 403)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Campaign to Retain and Attract Business in N.Y.
      - 1966 January - 1967 June (Box 154, Folder 404-418)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 155, Folder 419-424)
    - Research Subject File
      - Aging (Box 156, Folder 425)
      - Advisory Council (Box 156, Folder 426)
      - Assembly leader information (Box 156, Folder 427)
      - Alvarez, Fernando E. (Box 156, Folder 428)
      - AUFBAU (Box 156, Folder 429)
      - Aurelio (Box 156, Folder 430)
      - Bay Ridge (Box 156, Folder 431)
      - Bibliography, selected JVL (Box 156, Folder 432)
      - Biographical material, JVL (Box 156, Folder 433)
      - Biographics, campaign staff (Box 156, Folder 434)
      - Block parties (Box 156, Folder 435)
      - Brooklyn map (Box 156, Folder 436)
      - Bronx enrollment, Board of elections (Box 156, Folder 437)
      - California file (Box 156, Folder 438)
      - Campaign memoranda and correspondence (Box 156, Folder 439)
      - Campaign announcements by special committees or concerning speical projects (Box 156, Folder 440)
      - Campaign literature (Box 156, Folder 441-442)
      - Campaign, newspaper, "We - Five" (Box 156, Folder 443)
      - Candidates for public office (Box 156, Folder 444)
      - Canvassing (Box 156, Folder 445)
      - Canvassing manual (Box 156, Folder 446)
      - Case for Lindsay (Box 156, Folder 447)
      - Citizen's views on drug addiction (Box 156, Folder 448)
      - City charter revision (Box 156, Folder 449)
      - City College, answer to Jewish Congress (Box 157, Folder 450)
      - Concourse Action Program (Box 157, Folder 451)
      - Congressional (Box 157, Folder 452)
      - Constituent correspondence (Box 157, Folder 453)
      - Coordinators (Box 157, Folder 454)
      - Corporation letter (Box 157, Folder 455)
      - County committee lists (Box 157, Folder 456)
      - County leader biographical sketches (Box 157, Folder 457)
      - Crime (Box 157, Folder 458)
      - Vote (Box 157, Folder 459)
      - Correspondence with volunteers (Box 157, Folder 460)
      - Debates and interviews (Box 157, Folder 461)
      - Democrats, membership lists, club endorsements (Box 157, Folder 462)
      - Democrats for JVL (Box 157, Folder 463)
      - Demographic breakdown (Box 157, Folder 464)
      - DePinna, progress and miscellaneous thoughts (Box 157, Folder 465)
      - Economic Development Association (Box 157, Folder 466)
      - Education (Box 157, Folder 467)
      - Endorsements (Box 157, Folder 468)
      - Election day (Box 157, Folder 469)
      - Election day, irregularities report form (Box 157, Folder 470)
      - Election night floor plans (Box 157, Folder 471)
      - Election profiles (Box 158, Folder 472)
      - Election profiles, New York (Box 158, Folder 473-474)
      - Endorsements (Box 158, Folder 475)
      - Entertainers for JVL (Box 158, Folder 476)
      - Evaluation, potential campaign stops (Box 158, Folder 477)
      - Facts of interest (Box 158, Folder 478)
      - Fact sheets, including middle income achievements (Box 158, Folder 479)
      - Fact sheet, senior New Yorkers (Box 158, Folder 480)
      - Fact sheets to revise (Box 158, Folder 481)
      - Federal aid (Box 158, Folder 482)
      - Feldstein report, legal services report on election day irregularities (Box 158, Folder 483)
      - Finance committee fund raising meetings (Box 158, Folder 484)
      - Fiak, Sheldon - Jewish community (Box 158, Folder 485)
      - First congressional district, Craig Barnes (Box 158, Folder 486)
      - Fiscal (Box 158, Folder 487)
      - Fisher, Susan, memoranda (Box 158, Folder 488)
      - Fund raising (Box 158, Folder 489)
      - Fund raising, leaders, cocktail parties, general (Box 158, Folder 490)
      - Gala (Box 159, Folder 491-492)
      - Gala solicitation (Box 159, Folder 493)
      - Garelik, Sanford D., acceptance (Box 159, Folder 494)
      - Garelik, Sanford D., biography (Box 159, Folder 495)
      - Garelik, Sanford D., Chief Inspector (Box 159, Folder 496)
      - Get out and vote in primary! (Box 159, Folder 497)
      - Goodell, Charles E., Viet Nam (Box 159, Folder 498)
      - Guide for Lindsay Captains (Box 159, Folder 499)
      - Housing projects (Box 159, Folder 500)
      - Housing, capital construction, annual report (Box 159, Folder 501)
      - Housing (Box 159, Folder 502-503)
      - Independent party, petition sample (Box 159, Folder 504)
      - Independent party, petition, instruction (Box 159, Folder 505)
      - Inspectors manual, election day (Box 159, Folder 506)
      - Issues, abandoned cars (Box 159, Folder 507)
      - Issues, assorted (Box 160, Folder 508)
      - Issues, canvassing proposal (Box 160, Folder 509)
      - Issues, decentralization (Box 160, Folder 510)
      - Issues, police (Box 160, Folder 511)
      - Issues, statement of candidacy (Box 160, Folder 512)
      - Issues, positions on JVL (Box 160, Folder 513)
      - Issues, statements on JVL (Box 160, Folder 514)
      - Issues, miscellaneous notes (Box 160, Folder 515)
      - Issues, the Lindsay team (Box 160, Folder 516)
      - Jackson Heights (Box 160, Folder 517)
      - Javits, Jacob, Senator, Viet Nam (Box 160, Folder 518)
      - Jewish speech (Box 160, Folder 519)
      - Labor unions endorsement (Box 160, Folder 520)
      - Legislation (Box 160, Folder 521)
      - Literature distribution (Box 160, Folder 522)
      - "Look Who's with Lindsay" (Box 160, Folder 523)
      - Manhattan storefronts (Box 160, Folder 524)
      - Marchi, John, negative (Box 160, Folder 525)
      - Marchi research (Box 160, Folder 526)
      - Mayoral inaugural program (Box 161, Folder 527)
      - Mayor's letters (Box 161, Folder 528)
      - Mayor's letter answered (Box 161, Folder 529)
      - Mayor's Office, task force, Reorganization statements (Box 161, Folder 530)
      - Middle income (Box 161, Folder 531-532)
      - Middle income and construction achievement (Box 161, Folder 533)
      - Military voters ballot sheet (Box 161, Folder 534)
      - Monet exhibit invitation, fundraising (Box 161, Folder 535)
      - Morgan biography (Box 161, Folder 536)
      - Motor homes (Box 161, Folder 537)
      - National priorities, re-ordering (Box 161, Folder 538)
      - Neighborhood ads, comments (Box 161, Folder 539)
      - New campaign strategy (Box 161, Folder 540)
      - New fact sheets (Box 161, Folder 541)
      - New York City enrollment, Board of Elections (Box 161, Folder 542)
      - Office memoranda (Box 161, Folder 543)
      - Paper ballot (Box 161, Folder 544)
      - Pelham Bay (Box 161, Folder 545)
      - Perrotta, Fioravante G., acceptance (Box 161, Folder 546)
      - Perrotta, Fioravante G., biography (Box 161, Folder 547)
      - Perrotta, Fioravante G., Financial Administrator (Box 161, Folder 548)
      - Perrotta, speech (Box 161, Folder 549)
      - Perrotta, JVL, statement (Box 161, Folder 550)
      - Personal, civil service statement, JVL (Box 161, Folder 551)
      - Petition distribution (Box 161, Folder 552)
      - Petition operation (Box 162, Folder 553)
      - Petitions to vote, sample (Box 162, Folder 554)
      - Polling places, Brooklyn (Box 162, Folder 555)
      - Polling places, locations (Box 162, Folder 556)
      - Polling plans, complaint forms (Box 162, Folder 557)
      - Poll watchers, check list (Box 162, Folder 558)
      - Poll watchers, fund raising and volunteer letters (Box 162, Folder 559)
      - Poll wathcers letter, follow-up (Box 162, Folder 560)
      - Poll watchers training records, sample (Box 162, Folder 561)
      - Press office correspondence (Box 162, Folder 562)
      - Press office memoranda (Box 162, Folder 563)
      - Primary, arguments for Sep. (Box 162, Folder 564)
      - Primary store fronts (Box 162, Folder 565)
      - Prober - Human Resource Administration (Box 162, Folder 566)
      - Proccaccino, Mario, literature, completed issues (Box 162, Folder 567)
      - Priority maps (Box 162, Folder 568)
      - Public Works, Department of (Box 162, Folder 569)
      - Quotes (Box 162, Folder 570)
      - Quotes about Lindsay (Box 162, Folder 571)
      - Queens Village (Box 162, Folder 572)
      - Robbi letter, Marvin Schick (Box 162, Folder 573)
      - Reid, Fergus III (Box 162, Folder 574)
      - Registration Board for election day, sample forms, information forms (Box 162, Folder 575)
      - Registration drive (Box 162, Folder 576)
      - Registration drive, Harlem Democrats for Action (Box 162, Folder 577)
      - Reorganization, municipal Health Services (Box 162, Folder 578)
      - Rent Stabilization Law (Box 162, Folder 579)
      - Republican Clubs (Box 162, Folder 580)
      - Republican Executive Committee meeting, city-wide (Box 162, Folder 581)
      - Richmond enrollment totals (Box 162, Folder 582)
      - Speech kit, new (Box 163, Folder 583)
      - Speeches, recent positions (Box 163, Folder 584)
      - Solicitation letters, sample (Box 163, Folder 585)
      - Staff lists and memoranda (Box 163, Folder 586)
      - Storefronts (Box 163, Folder 587)
      - Storefronts, coordinators, primary (Box 163, Folder 588)
      - Storefront information (Box 163, Folder 589-590)
      - Storefronts, location (Box 163, Folder 591)
      - Strategy (Box 163, Folder 592)
      - Tax information (Box 163, Folder 593)
      - Telephoning kit (Box 163, Folder 594)
      - Telephone solicitation manual (Box 163, Folder 595)
      - Thank you correspondence (Box 163, Folder 596)
      - "The Record" (Box 163, Folder 597)
      - Transcripts, press conferences (Box 163, Folder 598)
      - Transit fares (Box 163, Folder 599)
      - Transportation (Box 163, Folder 600)
      - TV film (Box 163, Folder 601)
      - TV radio, newspaper lists (Box 164, Folder 602-603)
      - Urban Action Task Force (Box 164, Folder 604)
      - Urban priorities petition and ad (Box 164, Folder 605)
      - Video truck units (Box 164, Folder 606)
      - Volunteer activities (Box 164, Folder 607)
      - Volunteer information (Box 164, Folder 608)
      - Voter registration questionnaire (Box 164, Folder 609)
      - Wagner, Robert, Mayor (Box 164, Folder 610-612)
      - Wagner, Robert, Mayor (Box 165, Folder 613)
      - Wagner, negative research transcripts, anti-war quotes (Box 165, Folder 614)
      - Welfare, Lindsay's stand (Box 165, Folder 615)
      - Windsor (MPO cameras) (Box 165, Folder 616)
      - Women (Box 165, Folder 617)
      - Women's Committee to re-elect John V. Lindsay (Box 165, Folder 618)
      - World's Fair (Box 165, Folder 619)
      - Writers (Box 165, Folder 620)
      - Young Democrats for JVL (Box 165, Folder 621)
      - Year-end reviews (Box 165, Folder 622)
    - Correspondence
      - A (Box 166, Folder 623)
      - B (Box 166, Folder 624-625)
      - C (Box 166, Folder 626-627)
      - D (Box 166, Folder 628)
      - E (Box 166, Folder 629)
      - F (Box 167, Folder 630)
      - G (Box 167, Folder 631-632)
      - H (Box 167, Folder 633)
      - I (Box 167, Folder 634)
      - J (Box 167, Folder 635)
      - K (Box 167, Folder 636)
      - L (Box 168, Folder 637)
      - M (Box 168, Folder 638-639)
      - N (Box 168, Folder 640)
      - O (Box 168, Folder 641)
      - P (Box 168, Folder 642)
      - Q (Box 168, Folder 643)
      - R (Box 169, Folder 644)
      - S (Box 169, Folder 645-646)
      - T (Box 169, Folder 647)
      - U (Box 169, Folder 648)
      - V (Box 169, Folder 649)
      - W (Box 169, Folder 650)
      - XYZ (Box 169, Folder 651)
      - Congratulatory notes, unanswered, 1969-1970 (Box 170, Folder 652)
      - Congratulatory notes, 1969 November 5 - December 3 (Box 170, Folder 653)
      - Thank you letters, 1969 October 28 - 1970 January 14, February 3-7,10-28, March 2 - April 15 (Box 170, Folder 654-659)
      - Thank you letters, campaign show, 1969 October (Box 170, Folder 660)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1972; Series VIII
    Series VIII is sub-divided into the following sections:
    Press Releases and Editorials
    Daily Mentions in U.S. Newspapers
    Public Opinion Mail
    - Schedules
      - City Hall scheduling meeting, 1971 December 8 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Canton, Ohio, 1971 December 13-14 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - City Hall scheduling meeting, 1971 December 16 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Political scheduling meeting, 1971 December 17 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Milwaukee, 1971 December 19 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Florida, 1971 December 28 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Wisconsin, 1971 December 29 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Scheduling meeting, 1972 January 5 (Box 171, Folder 8)
      - City Hall scheduling meeting, 1972 January 6 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Florida, 1972 January 6-9 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - Massachusetts, 1972 January 13 (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - Arizona, 1972 January 15 (Box 171, Folder 12)
      - Political scheduling, 1972 January 18 (Box 171, Folder 13)
      - Florida, 1972 January 21-23 (Box 171, Folder 14)
      - Women's National Democratic Club, 1972 January 24 (Box 171, Folder 15)
      - Political scheduling, 1972 January 26 (Box 171, Folder 16)
      - Florida, 1972 January 27-28 (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases and Editorials
      - Arizona, Flagstaff (on seeking the presidency), 1972 January 15 (Box 172, Folder 18)
      - Bangladesh statement, 1972 February 24 (Box 172, Folder 19)
      - Berkley speech, 1972 April 2 (Box 172, Folder 20)
      - Blacks, undated (Box 172, Folder 21)
      - Boston speech, foreign policy, 1972 February 10 (Box 172, Folder 22)
      - California slates, 1972 February 24 (Box 172, Folder 23)
      - Colorado Steering Committee, 1972 March 1 (Box 172, Folder 24)
      - Connecticut head, 1972 March 13 (Box 172, Folder 25)
      - Corporate power (nader), 1972 March 8 (Box 172, Folder 26)
      - Dade Center, senior citizens, Miami, 1972 February 15 (Box 172, Folder 27)
      - Dade City Young Lawyers, Miami, 1972 February 15 (Box 172, Folder 28)
      - Debate challenge, telegram to all campaigners, 1972 February 15 (Box 172, Folder 29)
      - Democratic National Committee, undated (Box 172, Folder 30)
      - Fair share income, senior citizens, New York City, 1972 February 25 (Box 172, Folder 31)
      - Farmer's Union Convention statement, Texas, 1972 February 29 (Box 172, Folder 32)
      - Florida school superintendent endorsement, 1972 February 22 (Box 172, Folder 33)